A Guide to the City College of New York collection of the Russell Sage Foundation Library FA1208
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Industrial and Labour Index, Vol. 57-60 (Box 35)
- Industrial and Labour Index, Vol. 61-66 (Box 36)
- Educational Administration as Social Policy, 1934 (Box 36)
- A Tuberculosis Directory Containing a List of Institutions, Associations and Other Agencies Dealing with Tuberculosis in the United States and Canada, 1916 (Box 36)
- Health and Welfare Directory, Delaware, Montgomery and Philadelphia Counties, 1947 (Box 36)
- Adult Education: The Evening Industrial School, 1930 (Box 37)
- Principle, Policies, and Plans for the Improvement of the New Bedford Public Schools, 1922 (Box 37)
- Annual Report of Montefiore School, Seventh Annual, 1935-1936 (Box 37)
- Report of the Royal Commission on Dominion-Provincial Relations, Book 1: Canada, 1867-1939 (Box 37)
- A Tuberculosis Directory: Containing a List of Institutions, Associations, and Other Agencies Dealing with Tuberculosis in the Untied States, 1911 (Box 37)
- Digest of State Laws Relating to Taxation and Revenue, 1922, 1924 (Box 37)
- San Francisco Relief Survey the Organization and Methods of Relief Used After the Earthquake and Fire of 1906 April 18, 1913 (Box 37)
- Housing Comes of Age, 1938 (Box 37)
- The Defective in Speech, 1942 (Box 37)
- Housing America, 1932 (Box 37)
- First (Progress) Report, with Appendices and Supplements: Slum Reclamation - Housing for the Lower-Paid Worker - Short Term Program, 1937 (Box 38)
- Fundaments of Housing Study, 1938 (Box 38)
- Industrial and Labour Information Index, Vol. 67-72 (Box 38)
- Industrial and Labour Information Index, Vol. 73 (Box 39)
- Men Under Stress (Box 39)
- Men Under Stress (Box 39)
- Men Under Stress (Box 39)
- Men Under Stress (Box 39)
- The Psychology of Women: A Psychoanalytic Interpretation (2 Volumes) (Box 39)
- Social Work Year Book, Vol. 1-2 (Box 39)
- Social Work Year Book, Vol. 3-5, 8-9, 12 (Box 40)
- Primitive Labour, 1924 (Box 40)
- Small Holders: What Must they Do to Succeed: With a Chapter on the Revival of Country Life, 1909 (Box 40)
- Working Men's Social Clubs and Educational Institutes, Volume III, 1904 (Box 41)
- Patterns of Workers' Education, the Story of the Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1941 (Box 41)
- School Survey, Grands Rapid, Michigan, 1916 (Box 41)
- Encyclopedia of Religion and Ethics, 1922 (Box 41)
- Report on the Treatment of the surroundings of the Small Home Including, 1919 (Box 41)
- Training in Psychiatric Social Work at the Institute for Child Guidance, 1927-1933, 1934 (Box 41)
- Limbs for the Limbless, a Handbook on Artificial Limbs for Layman and Surgeon, 1934 (Box 41)
- The Management of Municipal Housing Estates, Report of the House Management and Housing Associations Sub-Committee of the Central Housing Advisory Committee, 1938 (Box 41)
- Housing for the Working Classes, How to Provide them in Town and Country, 1900 (Box 41)
- Housing Conditions in Fall River: Report Prepared for the Association Charities Housing Committee, 1912 (Box 41)
- Some Experiments in Housing, 1891-1901 (Box 41)
- First Report of the Cambridge Housing Association: Housing Conditions in Cambridge, 1913 (Box 41)
- War Neuroses in North Africa; Tunisian Campaign, 1943 January-May (Box 41)
- Rehabilitating Blighted Areas: Studies of Blighted Areas, How They Evolve and Their Effect on Society: a Plan for Their Rehabilitation and a Bibliography, Report of the Committee on Blighted Area Housing of the Architects Club of Chicago, 1932 (Box 41)
- The Housing Problem in Glasgow, 1907 (Box 41)
- Personal Observations of some Developments in Housing in Europe, 1914 (Box 41)
- Report of the South Wales Regional Survey Committee, 1921 (Box 41)
- Housing - The Growth of State Interest and Control and What it May Lead to (Being a Lecture Delivered Before the Royal Philosophical Society of Glasgow, 1920 December 1, 1921
- The Housing Problem, 1918 (Box 41)
- Report re: Housing for 1921, Including Town Planning of the Town of Kapuskasing, 1922 (Box 41)
- Scottish Land; The Report of the Scottish Land Enquiry Committee, 1914 (Box 41)
- Housing Conditions in Baltimore; Report of a Special Committee of the Association for the Improvement of the Condition of the Poor and the Charity Organization Society, Submitting the Results of an Investigation Made by Janet E. Kemp, 1907 (Box 41)
- Report of the Housing Committee: Presented to the Council, 1906 July 3 (Box 41)
- A Survey of the Tuberculosis Situation in the State of Ohio, 1912 (Box 42)
- The Housing of Amsterdam, New York: With Some Notes on the Prevalence of Tuberculosis, 1917 (Box 42)
- State Housing Agencies, 1942 (Box 42)
- A Resume of a Tuberculosis Survey of a Silk Mill Village in North Carolina, 1921 (Box 42)
- Beamten-Wohnungs-Verein zu Berlin, 1910 (Box 42)
- Unsere Wohnungs-Enquete im Jahre 1909, 1910 (Box 42)
- Boston's Housing Problem: Preliminary Report of a Committee Appointed by the Economic Club of Boston, 1911 (Box 42)
- A Report on the Building Department of the City of Boston, 1912 (Box 42)
- Report of Committee Appointed by Mayor Peters on Housing, 1919 (Box 42)
- Report of the Committee on the Expediency of Providing Better Tenements for the Poor, 1846 (Box 42)
- Kobenhavns Kommunes Bolig Foranstaltninger, 1930 (Box 42)
- Report on Dublin Housing, 1918 (Box 42)
- Report from the Town Clerk with Reference to the Housing of the Poor, 1900 (Box 42)
- Report of the Housing Commission, City of Des Moines, 1917 (Box 42)
- Housing Conditions in Denver, 1930 (Box 42)
- Report re Housing for 1919, Including Reports, 1920 (Box 42)
- A Tuberculosis Survey of New Jersey and Report, 1917 (Box 43)
- Handbook of Help for Persons Suffering from Pulmonary Tuberculosis (Consumption), 1909 (Box 43)
- Report on Survey of Housing Conditions: in Hatchett, Brearley, parts of Pritchett and Blews Streets, New Town Row and Summer Lane (in St. Mary's Ward), part of Cheapside (in St. Martin's Ward), Allison, Coventry, and Meriden Streets (in St. Bartholomew's Ward), 1929 (Box 43)
- A Brief Survey of Housing Conditions in Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1914 (Box 43)
- A Survey of Housing Conditions, Baltimore, Maryland, 1921 (Box 43)
- Housing Analysis of Attleboro, Massachusetts, 1921 (Box 43)
- When We Build Again, a Study Based on Research into Conditions of Living and Working in Birmingham, 1941 (Box 43)
- Housing, the Present Opportunity, 1918 (Box 43)
- Negro Housing Survey of Charleston, 1934 (Box 43)
- An Investigation of Housing Conditions of War Workers in Cleveland, 1918 (Box 43)
- Housing Conditions and Tendencies of Grand Rapids, Michigan: Report of the Housing Committee of the Charity Organization Society of Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1913 (Box 43)
- Second Report of the Tuberculosis Commission of Maryland, 1906 (Box 43)
- Report of the Special Recess Committee Appointed to Investigate Methods Employed in Checking the Spread of Tuberculosis, 1914 Janaury (Box 43)
- Report of the Commission to Investigate Measures for the Relief of Consumptives, 1907 January (Box 43)
- Report of the Tuberculosis Survey of the State Board of Health: for the Twelve Months from 1915 October 1-1916 October 1, Under the Provisions of Act 238 of the Public Acts of 1915, 1917 (Box 43)
- Rowton House, Camden Town, London, N.W.: A Description with illustrations. To which is Added Lord Rowton and Rowton Houses, 1905 (Box 43)
- Houses Conditions in a Liverpool Ward: Report of an Enquiry, 1930 (Box 43)
- Housing in Liverpool: A Survey, by Sample, of Present Conditions, 1930 (Box 43)
- The Housing Problem: Memorandum on "The Housing of the Dispossessed in Liverpool", 1916 (Box 43)
- The Housing Problem, with Special Reference to E.J. Smith's Bradford Scheme, 1918 (Box 43)
- The Housing Problem in Texas: A Study of Physical Conditions Under Which the Other Half Lives, 1911 (Box 43)
- New Homes for the Old, Publicly Owned Housing in Tennessee, 1948 (Box 43)
- Tenement Conditions in Chicago, 1901 (Box 43)
- A Problem for Tuberculosis Control in the State of Louisiana, 1924 (Box 43)
- Public Health Methods and the Application in Portland. A Preliminary Study, 1922 (Box 43)
- Housing Conditions in Main Line Towns, 1912 (Box 43)
- Costs of Dental Care for Adults Under Specific Clinical Conditions, an Exploration of General Issues on the Basis of Initial and Maintenance Care Experience of 485 Patients of Dental Health Service, New York City, 1943 (Box 43)
- Report of the Commission Appointed by the Mayor to Investigate Tenement House Conditions in the City of Boston, 1904 (Box 43)
- The People's Housing. The Effect of the Finance (1909-1910) Act, 1910 on the Building of Cottages, 1916 (Box 43)
- Before the United States House Committee on Public Buildings and Grounds, Sixty-Sixth Congress, first Session, 1919 November 12 (Box 43)
- The Future of Housing (Box 43)
- A Tentative Five Plan for Slum Clearance and Low-cost Housing in New Jersey, 1934 (Box 44)
- The Chicago Problem for Demolition and Rehabilitation of Sub-standard Housing, Report Submitted to Mayor Edward J. Kelly, 1935 October 15 (Box 44)
- Housing Progress in Puerto Rico, 1938-1948 (Box 44)
- Die Wohnungsnot in Frankfurt a.Main ihre Ursachen und ihre Abhilfe, 1912 (Box 44)
- The Falling Sickness: A History of Epilepsy from the Greeks to the Beginnings of Modern Neurology, 1945 (Box 44)
- Tuberculosis in Massachusetts, 1908 (Box 44)
- The Campaign Against Tuberculosis in the United States, Including a Director of institutions Dealing with Tuberculosis in the United States and Canada: Compiled Under the Direction of the National Association for the Study and Prevention of Tuberculosis, 1908 (Box 44)
- The Problem of Cerebral Palsy Today, 1947 (Box 44)
- Information for Parents of Cerebral Palsied Children, 1948 (Box 44)
- Twenty Questions on the Cerebral Palsied Child in California, 1948 (Box 44)
- Vocational, Educational, and Recreational Needs of the Cerebral Palsied Adult, A Survey of a Sampling of 200 Ambulatory Cerebral Palsied Adults in the New York City, 1953 (Box 44)
- The Study of Cerebral palsy in Connecticut, 1951 (Box 44)
- Conference on the Cerebral Palsied Child, 1946 April 3-4 (Box 44)
- Report of the Louisiana State Housing Commission. Under Authority of Act no. 19 of the General Assembly of 1920 of the State of Louisiana, 1921 September 28 (Box 44)
- Evaluating Rural Housing, the Development of the Florida Housing Inventory and the Index of Housing Adequacy, 1942 (Box 44)
- Development of Cooperative Farm Housing Research in the North Central Region, 1952 (Box 44)
- Report of the Homestead Commission Made Under the Provision of Chapter 714 of the Acts of 1912, 1913 (Box 44)
- Housing Conditions in Relation t Farm Labor Turnover: A Study of 1090 Farm Houses in Five Countries in Maryland, 1932 (Box 44)
- Rural Housing in Louisiana, 1937 (Box 44)
- Better Housing in Iowa (Bulletin No. 9), 1919 (Box 44)
- Final Report of the Illinois Housing Commission, 1933 April (Box 44)
- Toward Fuller Living Through Public Housing and Leisure Time Activities, 1934 (Box 44)
- Report on Housing Conditions in Kansas City, Missouri, Showing Defects in Present Laws and Suggesting Form of Code Needed, 1912 (Box 44)
- Report of the Proceedings Twenty-Ninth Meeting of the Convention of American Instructor of the Deaf, Jacksonville, Illinois (8 Volumes), 1935 June 17-21 (Box 45)
- Report of the Annual Conference of the American Federation of Organizations for the Hard of Hearing, Volumes 3-4, 11, 12-15 (Box 45)
- Der Wanderer, 1909-1913 (Box 45)
- Der Wanderer, 1914-1940 (Box 46)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work at the Forty-Eight Session Held in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1921 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work at the Forty-Eight Session Held in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1920 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fifth Annual Session held in the City of Richmond, VA, 1908 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fifth Annual Session held in the City of Richmond, VA, 1908 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fifth Annual Session held in the City of Richmond, VA, 1908 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fourth Annual Session held in the City of Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1907 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fourth Annual Session held in the City of Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1907 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Fourth Annual Session held in the City of Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1907 (Box 47)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction at the Thirty-Third Annual Session held in the City of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921 (Box 48)
- Broken Homes: A Study of Family Desertion and Its Social Treatment, 1919 (Box 48)
- Annual Report of the Board of Health of the Health Department of the City of New York for the Year Ending 1897 December 31, 1900 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventieth Annual Meeting War Regional Conference, 1943 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-First Annual Meeting Cleveland, Ohio, 1944 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-First Annual Meeting Cleveland, Ohio, 1944 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-First Annual Meeting Cleveland, Ohio, 1944 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Second Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Second Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Second Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 48)
- Proceedings of the National Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Second Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 48)
- Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Third Annual Meeting Buffalo, NY, 1946 (Box 49)
- Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Third Annual Meeting Buffalo, NY, 1946 (Box 49)
- Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Third Annual Meeting Buffalo, NY, 1946 (Box 49)
- Proceedings of the Nationals Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Fourth Annual Meeting San Francisco, California, 1947 (Box 49)
- Proceedings of the Nationals Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Fourth Annual Meeting San Francisco, California, 1947 (Box 49)
- Proceedings of the Nationals Conference of Social Work: Selected Papers Seventy-Fifth Annual Meeting Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1948 (Box 49)
- The Illinois Labor Bulletin, Volume 2-3 (Box 49)
- The Illinois Labor Bulletin, Volume 4-6 (Box 50)
- Report of the Registrar of Friendly Societies of Ontario, Volumes 1912-1919 (Box 50)
- Proceedings of the Fifty-Seventh Annual Conference, 1944 (Box 50)
- Annual Report of the Secretary for Mines and the Annual Report of H.M. Chief Inspector of Mines, Reports 1-22, 1927-1935 (Box 51)
- Readings in Abnormal Psychology and Mental Hygiene (Box 51)
- The Social Welfare Forum, 1950: Official Proceedings, 77th annual Meeting National Conference of Social Work, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1950 April 23-28 (Box 51)
- "Proceedings of the First National Conference on Infant Mortality and Public Welfare", 1921 December 6-10 (Box 51)
- International Review for Social History, Vol. 3 (Box 52)
- Abstract of Labour Statistics of the United Kingdom (4 Volumes), 1926, 1928, 1931, 1937 (Box 52)
- Abstract of Labour Statistics, Board of Trade (Labour Department), Sixth Annual Abstract of Labour Statistics of the United Kingdom, 1900 (Box 52)
- Board of Trade. (Annual Report of Labour Department.) Report on the Work of the Labour Department of the Board of Trade (1893-1894) with Supplement Containing Abstract of Labour Statistics (Box 52)
- Fourteenth Abstract of Labour Statistics of the United Kingdom, 1908-1909, 1911 (Box 52)
- Tenth Abstract of Labour Statistics of the United Kingdom, 1902-1904, 1905 (Box 53)
- Year Book City of Charleston, South Carolina, 1924-1930 (Box 53)
- Year Book City of Charleston, South Carolina, 1932-1951 (Box 54)
- Women's/Men Misdemeanants Division of the Municipal Court of Philadelphia; a Report by the Bureau of Municipal Research of Philadelphia of a Study Made by it as Agent of the Thomas Skelton Harrison Foundation (Volumes 1932 and 1932-1933) (Box 54)
- Twenty-Seventh Annual Report of The Associated Charities of Cambridge, 1909 November (Box 55)
- First Annual Report of the Associated Charities of Cambridge, 1883 October (Box 55)
- Ongevallenstatistiek betreffende het kalenderjaar (12 Volumes), 1952-1963 (Box 55)
- Rules and Classifications as Adopted 1899 July 11, with Amendments to 1903 July 9 (Box 55)
- Chicago Bureau of Public Efficiency Bulletins, 1911-1922 (Box 56)
- Chicago Bureau of Public Efficiency Bulletins, 1911-1922 (Box 56)
- Chicago Bureau of Public Efficiency Bulletins, 1911-1922 (Box 56)
- Chicago Bureau of Public Efficiency Bulletins, 1911-1922 (Box 56)
- Chicago Bureau of Public Efficiency Bulletins, 1911-1922 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1923 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1926 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1930 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1933 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1936 (Box 56)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1938 (Box 57)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1939 (Box 57)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1942 (Box 57)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1944 (Box 57)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1946 (Box 57)
- Social Service Directory Chicago, 1951 (Box 57)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1894 (Box 57)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1898 (Box 57)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1899 (Box 57)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1901 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1902 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1903 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1905 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1907 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1908 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1909 (Box 58)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1910 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1911 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1912 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1913 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1914 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1915 (Box 59)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1920 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1922-1923 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1925 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1926 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1928 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1929 (Box 60)
- Burdett's Hospitals and Charities: Being the Year Book of Philanthropy, 1930 (Box 60)
- Annual Report of the Council, Vol. 1, 1912 (Box 60)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1920-1924 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1924-1935 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1939 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1940 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1941 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1942 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1943 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1944 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1945 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1946 (Box 61)
- Georgia Department of Public, Report, 1949 (Box 61)
- American Association for Labor Legislation, Proceedings of the First Annual Meeting of the American Association for Labor Legislation, Madison, Wisconsin, 1907 December 30-31 (Box 61)
- Connecticut Humane Society, Annual Reports, 1892-1899 (Box 61)
- Connecticut Humane Society, Annual Reports, 1900-1908 (Box 61)
- Connecticut Humane Society, Annual Reports, 1909-1916 (Box 61)
- State Commission in Lunacy, Annual Reports of the Managers of the Utica State Hospital, 1896-1910 (Box 62)
- American Public Welfare Association, Public Welfare Directory, 1965 (Box 62)
- American Public Welfare Association, Public Welfare Directory, 1964 (Box 62)
- American Public Welfare Association, Public Welfare Directory, 1963 (Box 62)
- American Public Welfare Association, Public Welfare Directory, 1962 (Box 62)
- Georgia Department of Public Welfare, Report, 1938-1939 (Box 62)
- 55th Annual Report of the Inspectors of the State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, for the Year 1884, 1885 (Box 63)
- 49th Annual Report of the Inspectors of the State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, for the Year 1878, 1879 (Box 63)
- 45th Annual Report of the Inspectors of the State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, for the Year 1873 and 1874, 1875 (Box 63)
- 30th Annual Report of the Inspectors of the State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, 1859 (Box 63)
- 9th Annual Report of the Inspectors of the State Penitentiary for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania, 1838 (Box 63)
- Thirty-Second Annual Report of the Cleveland Humane Society, 1905 (Box 63)
- Annual Reports for Dr. Barnardo's Homes for Orphan and Waif Children, 1905-1911 (Box 63)
- Annual Reports for Dr. Barnardo's homes for Orphan and Waif Children, 1912-1919 (Box 64)
- Annual Reports for Dr. Barnardo's homes for Orphan and Waif Children, 1920-1926 (Box 64)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia, 1942 (Box 64)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1943 (Box 64)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1950 (Box 64)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1951 (Box 64)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1952 (Box 65)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1953 (Box 65)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1954 (Box 65)
- Boletín del Instituto Internacional Americano de Protección a la Infancia., 1955 (Box 65)
- Bulletin, Belgium, Office de la protection de l'enfance, 1920 (Box 65)
- Bulletin, Belgium, Office de la protection de l'enfance (2 Volumes), 1921 (Box 66)
- Bulletin, Belgium, Office de la protection de l'enfance, 1922 (Box 66)
- Annual Report of the Chicago Home for the Friendless, 1888-1898 (Box 66)
- Annual Report of the Chicago Home for the Friendless, 1914-1925 (Box 66)
- Jewish Orphan Asylum, Annual Report of the Board of Trustees and Directors of the Orphan Asylum, 1909-1917 (Box 66)
- Cleveland Protestant Orphan Asylum, Annual Report, 1907-1919 (Box 66)
- Jewish Orphan Asylum, Annual Report, 1900-1908 (Box 67)
- Leicester Charity Organisation Society Annual Report, 1919-1942 (Box 67)